Daniel Corbi Boldrin

Unity Software Developer

daniel_cboldrin@hotmail.com +1(416)876-2689 Toronto, ON, M6K 2G4

Highly focused software analyst and developer with 9 years of experience in a variety of development positions and projects.

I am organized, methodical, and have a keen eye for detailed results and solid coding in trustworthy business software, games, and apps.

I am very creative with visual and analytical problem-solving skills and I have broad experience with leadership of cross-functional teams of technical and non-technical personnel.

Experienced with software specification, requirement, design, and structure.

Work Experience

Unity 3D Developer

ZeMind – ON, Canada (remote)

November 2022 to present

Responsible for the development of Unity3D games and apps for iOS, Android, and Consoles.

[Placeholder for future updates]

[Placeholder for future updates]

[Placeholder for future updates]

• Unity VR Developer

Luxsonic – SK, Canada (remote)

August 2021 to November 2022

Participated in a team of 4 programmers to develop 4 immersive Unity VR software modules and platform. Those are used to train and assess medical personnel in diverse healthcare simulations, from microbiology lab simulations and blood transfusion methodologies, to cardiac and respiratory emergency procedures.

Experience with OpenXR, WaveXR, Oculus Quest and Vive Focus 3.

• Unity Game Programming Teacher

Halton STEM Club – ON, Canada (remote)

June 2021 to present

Responsible for planning, organizing, and teaching Unity3D game development, C# programming, 3D animation, and game design semi-private classes of 2 students from grade 6 to 10.

• Unity Game Programming Teacher

Wells Academy – ON, Canada (Remote)

February 2021 to October 2021

Planned, organized, and taught Unity3D game development, C# programming, 3D animation, modeling, and game design classes of 6 students from grade 6 to 10. Delivered personalized instructional feedback report cards to students and parents.

Unity Game Programming Teacher

Thinnox – ON, Canada (Remote)

June 2018 to December 2020

Planned, organized, and taught Unity3D game development, C# programming, 3D animation, modeling, electronic circuits, and game design classes for classes of 12 students from grade 6 to 12. Delivered personalized instructional feedback report cards to students and parents.

Analyst Developer

Programmers – SP, Brazil (Partially remote)

April 2016 to April 2017

Led a development team responsible for back and front-end programming of an automated medical survey system used over EUA.

Responsible for database management and software architecture using MVC5. Survey collected feedback via 30 online questions to be answered by patients after their visit.

Analyst Developer

Hewlett Packard (HP) - SP, Brazil

July 2015 to July 2016

Worked in a contingency team responsible for managing, monitoring, testing, and sustaining all 5 main systems fully functional. Experience with database jobs, bank applications, web pages, automatic emailing, and interactive voice response.

Analyst Developer

Líder Telecom – SP, Brazil

April 2013 to November 2014

Led a small team in various internal projects for the company, improving the quality of the calls answered by the telecom operators and overall work quality of employees.

Released applications that were used by 3000+ employees.

Developed databases and servers with several automatic routines. Experience with WAMP, LAMP, C# MVC, Aheeva, Active Directory, SQL, IIS.

Education

Game Programming – Advanced Diploma

George Brown College - Toronto, ON – Canada Graduated in April 2021

System Analysis and Development – Advanced Diploma

Federal Institute of São Paulo - Araraquara, SP - Brazil Graduated in January 2017

Skills

- Back-End: C# / C++ / C / Python / PHP / Java
- Front-End: HTML / CSS / JavaScript / jQuery / Kendo / AngularJS / React JS
- Database and Servers: SQL / MYSQL / IIS / Apache / Linux / Windows
- Game Engines: Unity3D / Unreal Engine / Construct / Scratch / Alice / OpenXR / WaveXR
- Versioning and revision control: GitHub / Perforce / SVN / Tortoise
- Frameworks and modules: XNA / Zend / Pygame
- Collaboration tools and websites: Slack / Trello / ClickUp / Repl.it / Tinkercad
- Arts: Photoshop / Blender / 3ds Max / Maya / Houdini / Realistic and Technical Drawing
- Other: Team leadership / Gameplay Programming / Prototyping / Agile development / Classroom management / Teaching / System Affordance /

Online Portfolio

https://danielboldrin.azurewebsites.net/